<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Stephen Morrissey</title>
    <link>https://stephenmorrissey.me/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://stephenmorrissey.me/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://stephenmorrissey.me/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://stephenmorrissey.me/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://stephenmorrissey.me/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://stephenmorrissey.me/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am passionate about new and innovate technologies, user-centered design, and data-driven development. Since starting off as a front end developer in the early 2000&amp;rsquo;s to positions in Program and Product, I have continued to keep my engineering skills fresh through courses and weekend projects. In Program and Product positions I have found it important to be able to translate effectively between different discipline groups whether that be UX, Technology or C-Suite Stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key accomplishments in my previous role at Sinclair have been 1) Managing from a program and then product perspective,100+ websites across the US such as komonews.com 2) Managing Integrations in the advertising space on Web, Mobile Apps and OTT (Connected TV&amp;rsquo;s such as Roku) with technologies such as Google Ad Manager, Rubicon Open Pre Bid, JWPlayer and SpotX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my time as a Technical Program/Project Manager,  I oversaw all facets of the project lifecycle; from planning, risk assessment, resource management, product development, QA to delivery. I believe the keys to a successful project are: 1) building strong working relationships with coworkers and clients 2) staying on top of current technologies with doing some quick projects 3) the ability to look at problems/opportunities from a high level and work backward from a common goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As mentioned, in my free time, I love working on weekend projects (kind of like my sudoku) with various colleagues, often building them from scratch or using a CMS  as the underlying framework. Having 7 years of experience working with custom CMS-driven websites using Drupal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I have been focussing on increasing my knowledge in the AI/ML space and working through various courses and projects such as: 1) Google Cloud Platform Fundamentals 2) IBM Data Science Certifications
I love a challenge, working with teams to structure a solution and then delivering that solution while monitoring impact.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
